All this Modi sahab Hindustan Unilever is
nearing 25, that
was a great call of yours, tell me what do you like now, it will be done
soon
and after that there will be a rally after moving away from profit booking, so
Asian
Paints is still on the list. I was
thinking a little bit away from Tantra Point video and
thinking about something new, so here what I like is
that digestive relative
growth and plot number 145 to 150, you
tell me, it should be available in metro, I have printed that if there was
some voltage in the morning, then
this limit which I am focusing on here,
now a good opportunity, you can see toe offers coming at that time, let's do this,
Avenger, let's
talk about some talks, you will see the index on the screen, in
between, Bajaj Finance
6450, what speed, God,
you are seeing this entire cement counters doing good bullishness,
such as Ultratech Ambuja and Ramco
Cement are seen coming in good mode here,
JK Cement is
creating around 3218 in the cash counter, let's add
Chandan Taparia snake here,
Chandan ji Bombay Stock  Look at the exchange, it's
very good. The fry section
can appear on your screen here. A good swing
high is already 34 rupees above. Tell me, if you
talk about the BSE set, we
saw selling from the upper levels for a long time. The last time it reached was
around 1410, which is
mid-July 2011. After that, Stark
gave a correction of about 20% from the top. The good thing is that now we are
seeing some good bottom reversal signs here.
You had supported the team 15 days ago
around 1070. Today, it
formed a low above 1084 and folded the statue
and is forming an equal central importance. So,
my most recent swing
corrective is now getting completed. It will take
support around 1090, 1100.
And it seems that now once it takes 1278, it will
show you this way, otherwise it will
also work. Remember, there
is a very developed strong chart of
BSE on this.  And stop the moment